adsterra.com 2016-06-13

# Privacy Policy - Adsterra. Premium International Advertising Network

Adsterra is committed to protecting the privacy of our online clients. This document outlines our technology and practices we use to collect information.

## WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT

Adsterra does not collect any personally identifiable information (PII) from users. Term “PII” generally refers to information such as an individual’s name, mailing address, phone number or e-mail address.

Adsterra offers a range of Services that allow advertisers and publishers to show online users the most useful and relevant ads online. Through the use of cookies and pixel tags, we collect anonymous usage statistics. These are industry standard technologies used by many major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. Information that is collected may include: session data, geography, browser information, IP address, operating system type.

## COOKIES AND PIXEL TRACKING

Adsterra uses cookies to enhance your browsing experience by preventing you from seeing the same advertisements repeatedly. To ensure the correct delivery and success of our customer’s advertising campaigns, we also use pixel tracking tags to measure usage statistics. Our customers will have their partner websites place these pixel tags on their websites. These tags allow our software to measure non-personal behavioral patterns which indicate the success of the advertising. No personally identifiable information is collected during this process.

## DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

Adsterra does not provide any of your personal information to our customers or their partners when you view an ad. The data we collect using cookies and pixel tags is only viewable by our customers and contains no personally identifiable information.

We may disclose a user’s information to third parties when we reasonably believe we are obligated to do so by law, and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including, but not limited to, fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person.

## CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## INFORMATION SECURITY

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect against the unauthorized access to, retention of, and disclosure of data. This includes undertaking necessary physical, electronic, and management activities required to protect data integrity, access, and use. Any data that is stored on our servers is treated as confidential information. Please keep in mind, however, that despite these reasonable efforts to protect data on our servers, no method of transmission over the Internet is guaranteed to be secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your data at all times, we cannot guarantee its absolute security and shall not be liable for any breach of security by an outside party.

## SPAM AND E-MAIL LISTS

We do not intentionally send unsolicited e-mail messages that could be construed as spam.

## CONTACT US

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using [this form.](https://adsterra.com/contact-us/)
